这家伙不关心我们做出的牺牲 先生
Hey, the man don't care about our sacrifices, sir.
是我们让他免遭大规模杀伤性武器的伤害
Keeping his ass safe from WMDs and stuff.
说实话 他把场地照看得很好
Well, to be fair, he does do a good job keeping up the grounds.
"芒果"
Hey, "Mango".
这草是不是特别绿
Doesn't all that green
让你想拿起割草机
make you just want to crank up that lawnmower
-修理一番  -这是人造草坪 傻逼
- and have a go at it? - It's AstroTurf, you moron.
别较真 别冲动
At ease, at ease, at ease.
抱歉 我们私底下就这么说话
My apologies, sir. That's just how we talk amongst ourselves.
厉害的垃圾话 我能听出来
I can appreciate good trash talk.
我听过更狠的 这种也还不错
It's not the best I've heard, but still pretty good.
-真的吗 谢谢了  -我想说
- Why, thank you, sir. - All I'm saying is,
墨西哥佬都喜欢...
any beaner would love a...
-放尊重点  -闭嘴 "芒果" 来吧
- Hey, show some respect. - Lock it up. Mango, come on.
老弟 拜托你听我的吧! 你必须听我的!